{
    "id": "b92edab689a0445d8120fab66173edd0",
    "title": "Possessive adjectives worksheet",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "f80bf6637d434117bccbf3eed40bdc6f",
            "title": "Possessive Adjectives Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Have you seen ............................... new coat?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "I",
                        "me",
                        "my"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "She has lost .................................... keys.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "she",
                        "her",
                        "hers"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Can I have a look at ................................... paper?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "you",
                        "your",
                        "yours"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The dog has had ................................... breakfast.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "it",
                        "its",
                        "it's"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Do you know ................................... name?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "she",
                        "her",
                        "hers"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is ........................................ plan?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "they",
                        "their",
                        "theirs"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Can you give me ................................. address?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "he",
                        "his",
                        "him"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He stood there with his hands in ............................... pockets.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "he",
                        "him",
                        "his"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I patted .................................. on the shoulder.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "she",
                        "her",
                        "hers"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I will agree to ....................................... suggestion if you lower the price.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "you",
                        "your",
                        "yours"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She is ................................... teacher.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "we",
                        "us",
                        "ours",
                        "our"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}